{
    "subject": "resource/Court_of_Assistants",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Livery_companies",
    "human_readable": "The subject of the Court of Assistants is Livery companies.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9410406947135925,
            "question": "What role does the Court of Assistants play in Livery companies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7679347991943359,
            "question": "What is the subject of the Court of Assistants?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6789267063140869,
            "question": "What is the purpose of Livery companies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6009000539779663,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of Livery companies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5713393092155457,
            "question": "Which organizations are governed by the Court of Assistants?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5615556836128235,
            "question": "What are some of the responsibilities of the Court of Assistants?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47075238823890686,
            "question": "Are Livery companies regulated by a governing body?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4291079044342041,
            "question": "How does the Court of Assistants make decisions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3705330193042755,
            "question": "How does the structure of Livery companies differ from other types of organizations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3163769543170929,
            "question": "Are there any historical examples of the Court of Assistants in action?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of the Court of Assistants is Livery companies.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3402_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the structure of Livery companies differ from other types of organizations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3402_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the Court of Assistants make decisions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3402_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are Livery companies regulated by a governing body?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3402_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3402_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3402_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3402_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3402_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3402_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3402_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3402_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3402_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3402_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3402_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide substantial information about the structure and operations of a Livery Company, including details on its Court of Assistants, Master, Wardens, Clerk, and other roles. The context clearly indicates that these Courts are associated with managing and overseeing Livery companies, which supports the statement that the subject of the Court of Assistants is indeed related to Livery companies."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}